Meeting Gorbachev is a documentary film directed by André Singer.
Mikhail Gorbachev, former president of the Soviet Union, sits down with
filmmaker Werner Herzog to discuss his many achievements.
Topics include the talks to reduce nuclear weapons, the
reunification of Germany and the dissolution of his country.
Self, played by Mikhail Gorbachev.
Self, played by Werner Herzog.
Self, played by Miklós Németh.
Self, played by Lech Wałęsa.
Self, played by George Shultz.
Self (archive Footage), played by George H. W. Bush.
Meeting Gorbachev is a 2018 biographical documentary film directed by Werner Herzog and André Singer
about the life of Mikhail Gorbachev, the eighth and last leader of the Soviet Union.
The film features three interviews between Herzog and Gorbachev, conducted over the span of six
months, and had its world premiere at the Telluride Film Festival on September 1, 2018.
The film ends with  Gorbachev reciting the poem "I Go Out
On The Road Alone" by Mikhail Lermontov.